

## Graphic Design + Marketing Specialist

# Jenna Howard

- Macon, GA
- jhoward.design
- **(**478) 719-0474

#### **Profile**

With 10 years in digital & traditional marketing, I specialize in turning ideas into powerful visual content. My expertise includes branding, strategy, graphic design, photography, and SEO. I've served a range of client sectors, ensuring each brand's voice resonates with their target audience.

#### **Skills**

- Active Campaign
  FIGMA
- MailChimp O Adobe Photoshop
- FacebookAdobe Illustrator
- Google Ads + Analytics
- Adobe PremierePro

## **Employment**

## 2020 - now Marketing Specialist at SPINEN

Translated ideas into concrete design for external clients & internal staff. Developed promotional materials including brochures, clothing, manuals, pens, PowerPoints, and signage. Managed social media pages & client interaction. Implemented digital ads that reached >30k people & newsletters that earned >\$30k in revenue.

## 2019 - now Freelance Graphic Designer

Overhauled client branding & content planning. Designed, developed, and maintained client websites, Google Business pages, & social media accounts. Started mailing list for customer newsletters. Produced brochures, menus, photo shoots, signage, & digital advertising. Reported client analytics.

#### 2018 - 2019 Project Manager at Third Wave Digital

Administered projects for national & small business campaigns. Executed complex digital communications on behalf of key clients (e.g. 7-Eleven) including 3rd party vendors. Maintained a visual matrix of both content & format variations for menu boards across region, store types, & times of day for >200 stores.

## Education

#### 2011 - 2015 Georgia College & State University

Bachelor of Arts in Mass Communication